<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet
      title="Verify Provisioning Entities">
  <intro>
      <description>
        This cheat sheet guides you through the provisioning entities created by the design pattern.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item
         skip="true"
         title="Verify Data Schema: DesignPatternSchema">
      <description>
		The data schema has a structure named <b>inputMessage</b>. This structure is used as the <b>Input Message</b> in the order recognition rule, and represents the incoming order. Other elements in the data schema include properties defined for the order item specification, like <b>LineId</b> and <b> LineName</b>.
      </description>
	  <command
            required="false"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.navigate.openResource(filePath=/OracleComms_OSM_DesignPattern_BaseOrchProject/dataDictionary/DesignPatternSchema.xsd)"/>
   </item>
    <item
         skip="true"
         title="Verify Role: admin">
      <description>
		The role created by the design pattern has all of the permissions selected by default.
      </description>
	  <command
            required="false"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.navigate.openResource(filePath=/OracleComms_OSM_DesignPattern_BaseOrchProject/model/admin.rolePermissions)"/>
   </item>
   <item
         skip="true"
         title="Verify Order: DesignPatternOrder">
      <description>
          Attributes that have been defined for the order item specification are added to the ControlData structure, which you can see in the <b>Order Template</b> tab.
	      <br/><br/>Select the <b>Details</b> tab on the order to see the values for <b>LifeCyclePolicy</b>,<b> Default Process</b>, and <b>Creation Task</b> that have been populated. 
	      <br/><br/>Select the <b>Amendable</b> tab to view or set whether the order can be amended. If the order is amendable, before you can deploy the cartridge you must define a <b>Key</b> value in this tab for the order to be created successfully.  You <i>must</i> replace the default value of <b>true()</b> in the <b>Expression</b> field with an XPath expression pointing to the data value on the order that is used to match the amendment order with the existing OSM order.
	      <br/><br/>The <b>Role</b> that has been created and assigned to the order is shown in the <b>Permissions</b> tab.
      </description>
	  <command
            required="false"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.navigate.openResource(filePath=/OracleComms_OSM_DesignPattern_BaseOrchProject/model/DesignPatternOrder.order)"/>
   </item>
   <item
         skip="true"
         title="Verify Order Lifecycle Policy: DesignPatternPolicy">
      <description>
		By default, the following transitions are enabled:
                <br/><b>Completed &gt; Update Order,</b> 
                <br/><b>In Progress &gt; Raise Exception,</b> 
                <br/><b>In Progress &gt; Update Order,</b> 
                <br/><b>Not Started &gt; Delete Order,</b> 
                <br/><b>Not Started &gt; Update Order</b>
      </description>
	  <command
            required="false"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.navigate.openResource(filePath=/OracleComms_OSM_DesignPattern_BaseOrchProject/model/DesignPatternPolicy.orderPolicy)"/>
   </item>
      <item
         skip="true"
         title="Verify Task: DesignPatternCreationTask">
      <description>
        	This manual task is used as the creation task for the order. The order item attributes have been added to the ControlData structure in the <b>Task Data</b> tab. The role is assigned to the task in the <b>Permissions</b> tab.
	 </description>
	 <command
            required="false"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.navigate.openResource(filePath=/OracleComms_OSM_DesignPattern_BaseOrchProject/model/DesignPatternCreationTask.manualTask)"/>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
